hi2world.com 2013-09-24

# Hi2World - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. Our privacy policy is set out below. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us through support@hi2mail.com  
  
---  
   
**The information Hi2 world receives and how it is used**  
  
We have access to any and all information you submit to our website \- for example, your email address if you provide it. We may use your email address to contact you with news about our services. If you want you can choose to unsubscribe of such communications contacting us.

Information we hold about you will never be revealed to a third party and will always remain confidential to Hi2 world and our staff unless you choose to publicly publish or share it with other users. We may collect data to enable us to recognise you and record how you use this website. This allows us to improve and personalise some of our services, and can save you from re-entering information when you return to this website.

We will regularly log your IP address. This is your computer's personal signature but is not linked to personally identifiable information. We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer and track the movements of users whilst on this site. We may share any IP addresses we obtain from abusive users amongst Hi2 world members in order to help protect the security of our site.   

**Your rights**  
  
We rarely hold or collect personally identifiable information on users however when we do, you have the right to see information held about you upon request. You can ask us to update or remove any personal information Hi2 world holds about you at any time by contacting us. We will always work to help you as honestly and speedily as we can.  

**More information**  
  
If you have any further questions, or want to know more, please contact us and we will reply within 18 hours.
